themefuse.com 2019-12-18

# Privacy Policy - ThemeFuse

Effective as of 1 July 2018

ThemeFuse LTD, (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the https://themefuse.com/ website (the “Service”).

At ThemeFuse, we care about the privacy of your data and are committed to protecting it. This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect about you and why, what we do with that information, and how we handle that information. We may change our privacy policy at any time without giving you notice, so please check it each time you visit our website.

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) is incorporated into ThemeFuse’s Terms of Service located at <https://themefuse.com/terms-conditions/> (the “Terms of Service”) and applies to the information obtained by us through your use of our Service as described in this Policy. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Policy. Capitalized terms used in this Policy and not otherwise defined shall have the meanings provided for those terms in the Terms of Service.

In this Policy, personal information means information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person. An identifiable person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, and online identifier or to one or more factors specific to his/her physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity. The use of information collected through our website and service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the services for which the Customers has engaged.

Our services may contain links to other websites, services, and the information practices and the content of such other websites are governed by the privacy statements of such other websites. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of any such other websites to understand their information practices.

## Information collection and use

We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third-party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Service’s functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.

Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and transferred to your device. We use cookies to collect information in order to improve our services for you.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. The Help feature on most browsers provides information on how to accept cookies, disable cookies or to notify you when receiving a new cookie.

If you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some features of our Service and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

The Site includes third-party social media features, such as the Facebook Like button, and third-party widgets, such as the ‘Share This’ button or interactive mini-programs that run on the Site. These features may collect your IP address and which page you are visiting on the Site, as well as set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Your interaction with these features is governed by the privacy policy of the third-party company providing it. Here are some examples of third-party social media features that we use, and their privacy policies:

You can generally activate or later deactivate the use of cookies through a functionality built into your web browser. To learn more about how to control cookie settings through your browser:

  * Click [here](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences) to learn more about managing cookie settings in Mozilla Firefox;
  * Click [here](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647) to learn more about managing cookie settings in Google Chrome;
  * Click [here](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-us/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies) to learn more about managing cookie settings in Microsoft Internet Explorer;
  * Click [here](https://support.apple.com/kb/ph21411) to learn more about managing cookie settings in Safari;
  * Click [here](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy) to learn more about managing cookie settings in Microsoft Edge.

If you want to learn more about cookies or how to control, disable, or delete them, please visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) for detailed guidance. In addition, certain third-party advertising networks, including Google, permit users to opt out of or customize preferences associated with your Internet browsing. To learn more about this feature from Google, click [here](https://adssettings.google.com/).

ThemeFuse LTD. uses remarketing services to advertise on third party web sites to you after you visited our Service. We, and our third party vendors, use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service.

Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page. Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page.

AdRoll remarketing service is provided by Semantic Sugar, Inc. You can opt-out of AdRoll remarketing by visiting this AdRoll Advertising Preferences web page.For more information on the privacy practices of AdRoll, please visit the AdRoll Privacy Policy web page.

We do not support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services and/or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform specific tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use your information for any other purpose.

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send or by contacting us.

We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our Service.

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, and we strive to implement and maintain reasonable, commercially acceptable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information we store, in order to protect it from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure.

However, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of the Personal Information we have collected from you.

## Changes to this privacy policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of March 19, 2018 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

If you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us.

ThemeFuse LTD.

hello@themefuse.com

We need cookies to run our site optimally, by continuing to browse you agree to our cookie policy for our required cookies. If you’d like to update your cookies, check out how to clear cookies for your browsers. Accept [Privacy & Cookie Policy](https://themefuse.com/privacy-policy/)
